CV - Gustav Bøgh

About me

Hello, I'm Gustav Bøgh, a 25-year-old multimedia design student with a focus on web development and digital marketing. My experience includes Frontend coding as well as Digital Marketing. I am enthusiastic about implementing effective Marketing Strategies and Web Solutions. I am dedicated to contributing to the development of online profiles, branding, and communication. I am seeking an opportunity where I can blend my frontend skills with my passion for digital marketing to make an impact.

Some of my projects

Student job:

 Oak | 8 – Instagram and Facebook SoMe Marketing presentation campaign https://www.instagram.com/oak8dk/ - https://www.facebook.com/oak8dk

1. Semester projects:

https://portfolio-gustavboegh.netlify.app/

2. Semester projects:

 https://ux-copenhagenteam1.netlify.app/

3. Semester (Frontend) projects:

https://gust0288.github.io/toDo App/

Video projects:

- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gEEXFLcVn3Y
- https://www.youtube.com/shorts/07kKNwjjKCY
- https://youtu.be/IVPgt-aQVQ0

- https://vildmad2sem.netlify.app/
- https://ca-kampagnesite.netlify.app/
- https://javaguitarscph.netlify.app/
- https://github.com/Gust0288/3sem exe
 rcises

Skills

Web development:

- HTML/CSS Advanced
- JavaScript Advanced
- JavaScript API handling— Advanced
- React Framework Intermediate
- Java Basic

Design/CMS tools:

- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, InDesign) Intermediate
- Figma Advanced
- WordPress Basic

Graphical design:

- Typography Basic
- Color theory Basic
- Layout design Intermediate

Multimedia production:

- Video editing (e.g., Adobe Premiere Pro) Advanced
- Video production (Sony, Canon etc.) Intermediate
- Sound editing (e.g., Adobe Audition) Basic

User Experience Design (UX):

• User testing - Advanced

- SQL Basic
- Responsive Web Design Advanced
- Astro Framework Advanced
- Database handling (Supabase, MySQL) Advanced
- Motion Design Basic

CV - Gustav Bøgh

- Wireframing Advanced
- Prototyping Advanced
- User experience testing Advanced

Marketing and Communication:

- Business model canvas (BMC) Intermediate
- SWOT Intermediate
- Value Proposition Canvas (VPC) -Intermediate
- Data and SoMe Analytics (Google Analytics)
 Intermediate
- Google Ads Intermediate

- Meta (Business suite/Ad manager) ads Intermediate
- Key Performance Indicators (KPI's) Intermediate
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Intermediate

Personal Qualifications

- Independent
- Passioned

- Flexible
- Ambitious

Work Experience

Year	Profession	Where	
2024 - now	Marketing Assistant/Student Assistant	Oak 8, Hellerup	
2024 - now	Marketing Assistant/Student Assistant	Maleea, Hellerup	
2023	Video Producer/Editor/Director	Oles Hus (Coffee and Wine Bar), Gentofte	
2023	Multimedia Design Student	Copenhagen School of Design and Technology,	
		Copenhagen	
2020 - 2024	Bartender	Oles Hus (Coffee and Wine Bar), Gentofte	
2020	Restaurant All-rounder	The Landing, Honeysuckle Dr, Newcastle NSW,	
		Australia	
2019	Bartender	Victoria Pub, Gammeltorv, Copenhagen	
2019	Bartender	Royal Arena (Concert Hall) VIP Lounge	
2016 - 2019	Bartender and Waiter	Chabber.com (freelance waiter)	
2018	Bartender and Waiter	Tribeca, Nørrebro, Copenhagen	
2017 - 2018	Lodge Waiter and Bartender	Odd Fellow Palæet, Copenhagen	
2016 - 2017	Leader/Key holder	LokalBrugsen, Virum	
2015 - 2016	Check-out Assistant	Fakta (supermarket), Kongens Lyngby	

Education

Year	School	Education/Degree	City
2023 - now	Copenhagen School of Design and Technology	Multimedia Design	Copenhagen
2021 - 2022	Copenhagen Business Academy (3 Semesters)	Computer Science	Copenhagen
2018 - 2019	Sergeant School – Danish Military (7 Months)	Sergeant (Non-commissioned officer)	Varde
2018	Aalborg Kaserne	National Military Service (Værnepligt)	Aalborg
2015 - 2018	Virum Gymnasium	Graduate	Virum
2014 - 2015	Kerteminde Boarding School	10th grade	Kerteminde
2004 - 2014	Kongevejens Skole	0-9th grade	Virum

Languages Danish (Native), English (Fluently), Norwegian (Conversational)